Right and Wrong no longer exist
Unthinkable is a drama, thriller film directed by Gregor Jordan.
The government gets wind of a plot to destroy America involving a trio of
nuclear weapons for which the whereabouts are unknown.
It's up to a seasoned interrogator and an FBI agent to
find out exactly where the nukes are.
Henry Harold 'H' Humphries, played by Samuel L. Jackson.
Agent Helen Brody, played by Carrie-Anne Moss.
Steven Arthur Younger, played by Michael Sheen.
Charles Thompson, played by Stephen Root.
Rina Humphries, played by Lora Kojovic.
Jack Saunders, played by Martin Donovan.
Unthinkable is a 2010 American thriller film directed
by Gregor Jordan and starring Samuel L.
Jackson, Michael Sheen and Carrie-Anne Moss.
It was released direct-to-video on June 14, 2010.
The film focuses on the sanctioned torture of a man who has threatened to
detonate three nuclear bombs, planted in three large U.S.
The film explores themes of psychological thriller,
videotape, hard, disturbed, philosophical.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending and thought_provoking.